eonlinegh.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy - EOnlineGH.Com

## What is this Privacy Policy for?

This privacy policy is for this website [www.eonlineghana.com] and served by [E! Online Ghana] and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it. The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

## The Website

This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.

## Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer / device. Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors. This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google’s privacy policy here for further information [ <http://www.google.com/privacy.html> ]. Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

###  **DISCLAIMER**

 **1\. Content**

The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect,will therefore be rejected.

All offers are not-binding and without obligation. Parts of the pages or the complete publication including all offers and information might be extended, changed or partly or completely deleted by the author without separate announcement.

 **  
2\. Referrals and links**

The author is not responsible for any contents linked or referred to from his pages – unless he has full knowledge of illegal contents and would be able to prevent the visitors of his site from viewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable for any postings or messages published by users of discussion boards, guestbooks or mailing lists provided on his page.

 **3\. Copyright**

The author intended not to use any copyrighted material for the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object.

The copyright for any material created by the author is reserved. Any duplication or use of objects such as images, diagrams, sounds or texts in other electronic or printed publications is not permitted without the author’s agreement.

 **4\. Privacy policy**

If the opportunity for the [input](http://draft.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=2320252734882398615) of personal or business data (email addresses, name, addresses) is given, the input of these data takes place voluntarily. The use and payment of all offered services are permitted – if and so far technically possible and reasonable – without specification of any personal data or under specification of anonymized data or an alias. The use of published postal addresses, telephone or fax numbers and email addresses for marketing purposes is prohibited, offenders sending unwanted spam messages will be punished.

 **  
5\. Legal validity of this disclaimer**

This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the content or validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact.

If you own any music that is posted on the site and would like to request it to be taken off please email me with proof of ownership and I will take the link down withing 3 business days.

### CONTENT REMOVAL

On this website (EonlineGhana.Com) you find links that lead to media files. These files are stored somewhere else on the internet and are NOT a part of this website. We do NOT carry ANY responsibility for them, We ONLY COLLECT links and INDEXES other sites contents.

If your copyrighted material has been indexed by EonlineGhana.Com and you want this material removed, you must provide a written communication with exact reference to the content you claim ownership to. This message must contain following:

Name and the exact URL of your copyrighted material.

Contact information so that we may contact you (street address, phone and email).

Clear proof of evidence that you own the copyright to said content or evidence that you are a representative of the person/company owning the content.

For such a request , please mail us directly at ADMIN [AT] EONLINEGHANA.COM

We suggest that if you really want to permanently remove your copyrighted material from the internet, you should contact the administrator of the physical URL where your copyrighted material is hosted.

We will reply to and clear EVERY request. We will not reply to automatized bot messages though, or messages missing any information listed above. Please notice it may take up to 72 hours to process your request. Don’t bother sending your request to our ISP, hosting company or anyone else – it will only take MORE time to process your request, as all messages are forwarded to the email address above.

## Resources & Further Information

  * [Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 – The Guide](http://www.ico.gov.uk/for_organisations/privacy_and_electronic_communications/the_guide.aspx)

v.3.0 September 2018 Edited & customised by:  E! Online Ghana

——————————————————————————- ——————————————————————————-

Stay connected on our website here: [http://www.eonlineghana.com](https://www.eonlineghana.com/)

Find us on facebook here: [http://www.facebook.com/eonlineghana](http://www.facebook.com/eonlineghana)

Find us on twitter here: [http://www.twitter.com/eonlinegh](http://www.twitter.com/theprincelive)

Hope you found this policy useful and any related links on the page. End of Privacy Policy.
